{
    "id": "112719c366a9464f9c6fc8d61b406673",
    "title": "Adding Contradictory Remarks",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He can speak English ........................... I can’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "But",
                "And"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "82e5cc034d474fa092f42d7d8f18b58c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won the test. ................................ his brother didn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "But",
                "And"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77a73b12eaf04bd49a3538fd24cc6646"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like reading comics. .................................. my wife doesn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "But",
                "And"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd61995b1cab4bcea4d7bcd0a8323eb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................. me well but his wife doesn’t",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knows",
                "doesn't know"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6a3322709274a70bb1618308e298ff7"
        },
        {
            "question": "English is easy to learn but French ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "isn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d7e4a0f108e4ae4ae4ef6f7a8e7f1d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did the homework but others .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1019ae97dcae446182f304212b2c78bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have learned classical music but my sister ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5a5e4bf8c4f48b782c1190e20c1e256"
        },
        {
            "question": "John .............................. but Peter hasn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has arrived",
                "hasn't arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "74fa6a10a7de463f9501bb6d380cb57e"
        },
        {
            "question": "James can sing well but Alice ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "can't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aacebb2b3aeb4f4d8ad0a1399932205a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will leave tomorrow  .................................... I won’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d49ce6c48c734be1933e56f847879ac0"
        }
    ]
}